<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Abe Burnett</title>
 <link href="http://abeburnett.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://abeburnett.github.com/"/>
 <updated>2013-10-04T17:10:27-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://abeburnett.github.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Abe Burnett</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>I built this blog, but I don't like it</title>
   <link href="http://abeburnett.github.com/blog/I-built-this-blog-but-I-dont-like-it"/>
   <updated>2013-10-04T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://abeburnett.github.com/blog/I-built-this-blog-but-I-dont-like-it</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;span9 columns&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Wow&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;So I followed the tutorial I discovered at Eric Jones blog (&quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://erjjones.github.io/blog/How-I-built-my-blog-in-one-day/&quot;&gt;How I built my blog in one day&lt;/a&gt;&quot;) thinking that it would yield a very nice, simple, direct coding blog here on github.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Ugh.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Seriously, if this is the alternative then I&#39;m not sure Wordpress has anything to worry about. Granted, this was an excellent educational experience, but beyond that, I&#39;m not very impressed.
      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      I have a basic blog, but it took hours to set-up, it doesn&#39;t look very good, and--apparently--I have to write posts for it in HTML.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      One of the reasons that Eric (? maybe it was someone else) gave for pursuing a non-Wordpress alternative was that he felt that using Wordpress ruined his coding &quot;cachet.&quot;
      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      Well, I guess I&#39;m not too worried that someone is going to look at my Wordpress blog and think &quot;oh, geez, who the heck is this guy--clearly he can&#39;t code.&quot; And if someone is dumb enough to think that, they&#39;re not someone I&#39;m too interested in doing business with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      I use Wordpress because, personally, I find it easy to create a nice looking, highly functional blog: one which is very easy to modify and change in any conceivable way, but also extremely efficient for blogging on.
      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      Personally, I&#39;ve never really understood all the furor over Wordpress. It seems to me to be much ado about nothing. I mean, do we really need Ghost? For those who don&#39;t know, Ghost is a minimalist blogging platform--created under the auspices that blogging on Wordpress is so tedious and difficult.
      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      But for me, blogging on Wordpress is a cinch for my needs. And that&#39;s what I&#39;m using. Simply writing this single post in HTML has been...well, gross. I avoid HTML even when coding because it&#39;s difficult to digest, and my fingers hate all the extra keystrokes. I use HAML, Slim, or Jade instead. I&#39;d rather deal with their idiocyncrasies than wrangle HMTL. Yuck.
      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
      For those who are looking for my real blog. Please go &lt;a href=&quot;http://abeburnettcoding.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;span9 columns&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Comments Section&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Feel free to comment on the post but keep it clean and on topic.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div id=&quot;disqus_thread&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
            /* * * CONFIGURATION VARIABLES: EDIT BEFORE PASTING INTO YOUR WEBPAGE * * */
            var disqus_shortname = &#39;abeburnett&#39;; // required: replace example with your forum shortname
            var disqus_identifier = &#39;/blog/I-built-this-blog-but-I-dont-like-it&#39;;
            var disqus_url = &#39;/blog/I-built-this-blog-but-I-dont-like-it&#39;;

            /* * * DON&#39;T EDIT BELOW THIS LINE * * */
            (function() {
                var dsq = document.createElement(&#39;script&#39;); dsq.type = &#39;text/javascript&#39;; dsq.async = true;
                dsq.src = &#39;http://&#39; + disqus_shortname + &#39;.disqus.com/embed.js&#39;;
                (document.getElementsByTagName(&#39;head&#39;)[0] || document.getElementsByTagName(&#39;body&#39;)[0]).appendChild(dsq);
            })();
        &lt;/script&gt;
        &lt;noscript&gt;Please enable JavaScript to view the &lt;a href=&quot;http://disqus.com/?ref_noscript&quot;&gt;comments powered by Disqus.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;http://disqus.com&quot; class=&quot;dsq-brlink&quot;&gt;blog comments powered by &lt;span class=&quot;logo-disqus&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;!-- Twitter --&gt;


&lt;script&gt;!function(d,s,id){var js,fjs=d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];if(!d.getElementById(id)){js=d.createElement(s);js.id=id;js.src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot;;fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js,fjs);}}(document,&quot;script&quot;,&quot;twitter-wjs&quot;);&lt;/script&gt;




&lt;!-- Google + --&gt;


&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
  (function() {
    var po = document.createElement(&#39;script&#39;); po.type = &#39;text/javascript&#39;; po.async = true;
    po.src = &#39;https://apis.google.com/js/plusone.js&#39;;
    var s = document.getElementsByTagName(&#39;script&#39;)[0]; s.parentNode.insertBefore(po, s);
  })();
&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>